- Hey, what's up, I'm Tom. - I'm Zendaya. - Jon. - I'm Sadie. - I'm Jacob. - And today, with the cast of "Spider-Man: Brand New Day," we are taking GQ's pop quiz. [fun music] - [Host] Round one, general comic trivia. - Oh, no. - [Host] What iconic line did Uncle Ben say to Peter Parker? - Aw, dammit. - "With great power comes great responsibility." - [Host] Perfect. - Fair and square. - [Host] Next question, who created Spider-Man? - Aw, damn. - Aw, [ __ ]. - Stan Lee and Steve Ditko. - [Jacob] Wow. - [Host] Point for Tom. - [Jacob] Dammit. - [Host] What super villain does Ned Leeds become in the comics? - The Hobgoblin. - [Host] That's correct. - Win today. - Really? - Hobgoblin. - Win today. - [Host] It's gonna get harder, guys. What did Mary Jane say to Peter the first time- - "Face it, tiger, you won?" Like, "face it, tiger, face it, tiger." - [Host] Half, I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna hold on. If someone can the full sentence. - "You hit the jackpot. Face it, tiger, you hit the jackpot." - [Host] There you go, that's correct, point to Zendaya. - Really did. - [Host] All right. Which issue of "The Amazing Spider-Man" did The Punisher first appear? - Oh, I don't know, I actually don't know. - Wait, which what? - [Host] Which issue of "The Amazing Spider-Man" did The Punisher first appear? - Over to you. - 143. - [Host] 129. - That was good though. - Ballpark. That was in the ballpark. - Pretty close. - [Host] Pretty close. Last question in round one. Who wrote the original comic's run of "Brand New Day?" - Oh damn. - We should all know this. - Embarrassing, we love you. - We love you. - [Host] The answer is- - Someone from Sony. Oh, go on. - [Host] Dan Slott. - Dan Slott. - Sorry, Dan. - Shout out. - Shout out. - Shout out Dan. - [Host] Round two, this is MCU, sort of wider MCU multiverse knowledge. - Nice, nice. - Uh oh. - [Host] What high school did Peter, MJ and Ned attend? - Midtown. - [Host] Full title? - High. - Midtown High. - Oh, sorry, sorry. - [Host] I'll accept it. - Midtown School of Science and Technology. - Oh, Midtown, yeah, okay. - Science and Technology. Yeah, yeah, yeah. - [Host] I'll accept it. Question two, what did Peter say to Dr. Strange after introducing himself in "Avengers: Infinity War?" - Oh, I don't know. - I say, oh, we're using, oh no, no, we're making our, we're making our used up names. Used up names? - "We're using our made-up names." - That's what I was trying to say. - You were like jumbling, bro, you were stumbling. - I'm so tired. - You can give it to him. - We're making our used up names. - I just was helping. - Why do I keep? We're making our- - We're using. - "We're using our made-up names," there you go. - [Host] I think I'm gonna have to give to Zendaya because you got it correct. - It's a half, maybe we can split it. - Yeah, you're right. - [Host] In "Spider-Man: No Way Home." - Oh yeah. - [Host] What did Peter 3, Andrew Garfield, think the Avengers were? Tom. - A band. - [Host] That's correct. - You wanna contribute Jon at some point? - I'm there, I'm- - He's coasting. - Yeah, I'm sending good vibes. - "I'm sending good vibes." - [Host] What pizza place did Peter Parker work in the Sam Raimi "Spider-Man 2?" - It didn't even go off. Joe's Pizza. - [Host] That is correct, Jacob, you're on the board. - Bang. - [Host] What villains did Peter Parker fight in "The Amazing Spider-Man 2?" - Aw, man. - [Host] Tom. - Rhino, Electro, Green Goblin and that's it, right? - [Host] That's it, that's it, you got it. - I was gonna say, there's- - There might have been another one, yeah, right, right. - [Host] What was the name of Spider-Man's mecha in the Japanese television series? - His mecha suit. - [Host] Mecha droid. - Yeah, yeah. - Mecha Droid? - [Host] Leopardon. - Oh. I would not have got that. - [Host] It was a weird show, guys. - It's a deep cut. - Yeah, that's a deep cut. - [Host] Round three, this is production knowledge. Who filmed Tom Holland's audition video? - Let's go. Let's go. - You know what, I it it first. I'm gonna let you have this though. - Thank you, you're so awesome. Jonathan Edward Bernthal. - Hey, let's go, let's go. - [Host] We'll give it to Jon. - I got that last. That's so pathetic. - [Host] What did Willem DaFoe wear on set to prevent his appearance in "Spider-Man: No Way Home" from being leaked? - I honestly forgot. - [Host] I think that was Zendaya, that was you. - Everyone wore cloaks. - [Jacob] Yeah. - [Host] Who played Miles Morales's uncle in "Spider-Man: Homecoming?" - [Jacob] Aw man. - Donald Glover. - [Host] That's correct. Name both of Tom's stunt doubles. Jacob. - Dave and Luke. - Yeah, that's technically correct. - That's technically correct. - That is technically correct 'cause there has been a bunch of stunt doubles. - And there's more. - And Chris. - Yeah, right, other ones from the other movies as well. - But that is, that's technically correct. - We've had a lot but yeah, that's technically correct. Yeah. - [Host] Give it to Jacob. All right, what two other Marvel projects has "Spider-Man: Brand New Day" director Destin Daniel Cretton directed? - "Wonder Man" and "Shang-Chi." - [Host] That's correct. - That was kind of close. - [Host] It was close, it was close. - I don't know. I'll let you have it though. - Thanks. - [Host] What show had Spider-Man's first live action appearance? - It's that TV show, isn't it? - [Host] You're on the right track. - He had his own TV show. - Yeah, I just don't know was it was called. - It was just called "The Amazing Spider-Man," right? - [Host] "The Electric Company." - Wrecked. The way that you replied was like, it was like really close- - It's not that. - [Host] It was a TV show. - Right, right. - [Host] It was a TV show. - Guy's like, no, right, yeah. - [Host] Okay, so this is finish the line. So basically, I'm not gonna tell you who said it but if you can figure out what the second half of the line is. - Okay. - [Host] Buzz in. "You know, I'm something of." - [Both] "A scientist myself." - But he, he, I didn't hit it fast enough. - [Host] Yeah, I think Tom got it. "That's my secret, Cap." - What? - [Host] "That's my secret, Cap." "That's your secret, Cap." - You say that? - I didn't say that. - [Host] You didn't say that, no one here said that. - Something Tony Stark would say? - "It's my secret, Cap." - But is it Spider-Man specific? - No, I don't think so. - [Host] It's wider MCU. - Yes. - [Host] It's someone that is in this movie said this. - Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, it's Mark Ruffalo. It's Mark Buffalo, the Hulk. He says, "It's time you get angry" and he goes, "that's my secret, Cap, I'm always angry" and then he goes- - [Host] There you go, that's correct. It's a point to Tom. - That was good. - [Host] Here's another one. "One batch, two batch." - "Penny and dime," let's go. - Damn, I would've never known. - [Host] That's another point for Jon. - It's crazy when that happens, isn't it? - [Host] Next line, "The power of the sun." - "In the palm of my hand." - [Host] That's correct, Otto Octavius, awesome. - Oh yeah, when he's making like that thing. - [Host] "If you're nothing without this suit." - "Then, then you shouldn't have it." - [Host] That's right, Tony Stark. - Yes. - Yes. Bang, Iron Man. - [Tom] Well done. - [Host] "I resent that. Slander is spoken." - Whoa. - Can we hear it again? - [Host] Absolutely, "I resent that. Slander is spoken." - I don't know. - [Host] I'll give you a hint. Another line this person typically says like, "I trust my barber." - What the [ __ ]? - [Host] "Give me pictures of Spider-Man." - Oh, it's J. Jonah Jameson. - Yeah but what does he say though? - And the line is? - [Host] In print, it's libel. - Spider-Man wasn't attacking the city. He was trying to save it, that's slander. - It is not, I resent that. Slander is spoken. In print, it's libel. - You don't trust anybody, that's your problem. - I trust my barber. - I would never have got that. - So nobody gets a point, you're supposed to finish it. - [Host] I'm trying to mess with you guys. - Yeah, I see. - [Host] Round five is we're gonna have a draw Spider-Man competition. - Sadie, you gotta at least win this one, bro. You gotta hit this one. - [Host] Sadie, I believe in you. I'm gonna give you guys a minute. - Oh okay. - [Host] All right, in three, two, one, go ahead. - He's already going. I made a bad shape, I made a bad shape. - Nice. - [Tom] Oh [ __ ]. - Oh my God. - [ __ ] this up. - Aw, it's going so sideways. - "Sideways." - I [ __ ] this up already. - [Host] 10, nine, eight- - He also wears little boots too kind of. - Oh yeah, his little boots. - Boots are going. - [Host] Five, four, three, two, one. All right, pencils down, everybody. - I don't want to. - Okay. - [Zendaya] I like the buildings. - Yeah, the buildings, actually, the webs. I like the spread of webs. - And it's got a scene. - Yeah, it makes more sense. - A little abstract, you know? - Jacob, let me see what you got. - [Zendaya] Okay. - [Jon] You definitely won. - Yeah, I think Sadie might have killed it, yeah. - [Tom] I think Sadie wins that. - No. - Yeah, the web- - We just went with the belt. - Yeah. - Just the belt. - Just the belt. - A simplified suit if you will. - I was like, do you even wear a belt? - That's really good. - That's a really great one. Actual symbol of the- - I like yours. - It's bad, I started with this and then I saw Zendaya's and I tried to get the eyes different. - The grand formation. - Yeah. - [Host] By vote, who do you think won? Is it Sadie? - Sadie. - For sure. - [Host] Sadie? - There was so much detail. - And there's way more to it, yeah. - 'Cause I gave up. - [Host] Well, Jacob breaks the set. I'm gonna give Sadie the point by Democratic vote. So guys, this is the rapid fire round, last round. How many Spider-Man films are there, films starring Spider-Man? - Eight. Nine. Nine, there's nine. - [Host] There are technically 14. - Damn 'cause there's like animated ones. - Yeah, not just the live action ones, yeah. - [Host] Who plays Spider-Man 2099 in "Into the Spider-Verse?" - [Jacob] I don't know what his name is. - It's the guy with the big daggers. - The punk one? - No, no, he's like the big mashing one. - Like who plays him? - Like who plays or- - [Host] Who does the voice? - Who does the voice. - [Host] I'll give you a hint. He is in "Star Wars" and "Dune" and "Inside Llewyn Davis." - Oh. - [Jacob] He's a big guy. - Why am I all of a sudden my brain is not, cannot function? - Help me. - On vacation with each other. - Oscar Isaac. - Oscar Isaac. - [Host] Oscar Isaac, I'll give it to Zendaya. - Yeah. - [Host] Where is Peter Parker from? - Queens. - [Host] Queens. Sadie, you were close, but. - Sorry, Sadie. - It's all right, no, no, no, you take it. - [Host] Next question is what was Peter Parker's first line in "Captain America: Civil War?" Tom. - "Fine." - [Host] "Hey, May." - Fu. Fu. - Fu. - Yes, you're right. "Hey, May" then I say "fine" and then I say something like "there's a crazy car parked outside" and then I see- - Nice Peter Parker voice. - Thanks. - Robert Downey Jr. - [Host] The next question is what was the last thing Peter said to Tony Stark "in Avengers: Infinity War?" Zendaya. - "I don't wanna go, I don't wanna go" and then we've been through this. - Nope. - It's not "I don't wanna go?" - [Host] Tom, buzz in. - I say, "I'm sorry." - [Host] Perfect, point for Tom. - He goes, not you. - [Host] And this one's a toughie. When is the first time, technically, that Spider-Man appeared alongside the X-Men in live action? - Wait, wait, sorry? - Technically? - [Host] When is the first time Spider-Man appeared in live action alongside the X-Men? - No idea. - Is it when he like went onto their set one time and he like, and it was like a joke, was it? - [Host] Jacob, that is 100%. - Was that the one? Yeah. Yeah. - How do you know that? - Yeah, well, I remember watching this video because I was up late at night and one of them was like a random fact about like 2002 movies and they were doing it at the same time, right? They were like filming the same time or something like that? - [Host] There were filming around the same time, yeah, and then it's a blooper on the DVD extra. - Yes. - Wait. [everyone laughing] I am completely in the wrong movie. I am so sorry. - [Host] Wow, Jacob. I didn't think anyone was gonna get that. - That was good. - [Host] All right, so- - I should win though. - [Host] I mean, for that alone. The final score is Sadie with one point. Jon, you have two points. Jacob, you came in with four points. Zendaya, you have a total of seven points. And Tom, you win this pop quiz with a total of 10 points. You are the winner of the GQ pop quiz. - Boo. - Boo. - [Jacob] Boo. - I've been playing this character for 10 years. It's the pride of my life. Seems like you guys have got to do a little bit more research before you grace the sets yet again. Thank you. - I don't know. - I don't know about that, yeah. - I feel like we can run a few things back. - Yeah, for sure. - I could have gotten a couple more, you know?